Finding Aid for the George P. Johnson Negro Film Collection LSC.1042
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Research Files
  - B
    - Buck and Bubbles
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 242, Atlantic City. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 188-192. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 236. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 659-672. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 817, A Song is Born. (Reel 11)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 780-781, A Cabin in the Sky. (Reel 12)
    - Buck Benny Rides Again (Paramount, 1940); Frame(s) 186. (Reel 2)
    - Buck, Leon, Frame(s) 187, Harlem on the Prairie. (Reel 2)
    - Buffalo Soldiers, (1959); Frame(s) 193-194. (Reel 2)
    - Bufford, Daisy
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 196. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 583, Hollywood productions. (Reel 5)
    - Buford, Freddie, Frame(s) 197. (Reel 2)
    - The Bull Drew Aces (Rochester, 1955); Frame(s) 195. (Reel 2)
    - Bullets or Ballots (1st National, 1936); Frame(s) 198, Louise Beavers. (Reel 2)
    - Bullfrog in the Sun (Nigram Corp.), Frame(s) 535. (Reel 9)
    - The Bull's Eye (Universal, 1918); Frame(s) 199, Noble Johnson. (Reel 2)
    - Bumbry, Grace, Frame(s) 499, Negro entertainers; 511, 515. (Reel 4)
    - Bunche, Ralph J.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 200-214. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 491, Hell has no Gates. (Reel 5)
    - Burbridge, Edward, Frame(s) 215-216. (Reel 2)
    - Burden of Truth (Allender Productions, 1958); Frame(s) 217. (Reel 2)
    - Burgess, Dorothy, Frame(s) 218. (Reel 2)
    - The Burglar, Frame(s) 219, James Leonard. (Reel 2)
    - Burke, Georgia
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 121-124, Anna Lucasta. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 220, Anna Lucasta. (Reel 2)
    - Burks, Donny, Frame(s) 384. (Reel 9)
    - Burleigh, Harry T.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 588-627, Birth of a Race; 604 Birth of a Race. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 910, William Grant Still. (Reel 11)
    - Burn, Frame(s) 407, 538. (Reel 9)
    - Burn, Killer, Burn (Embassy, 1963); Frame(s) 221. (Reel 2)
    - The Burning Cross (Screen Guild, 1947); Frame(s) 222. (Reel 2)
    - Burns, Fannetta, Frame(s) 556-557, His Great Chance. (Reel 5)
    - Burns, Sandy, Frame(s) 556, His Great Chance. (Reel 5)
    - Burrell, Walter
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 223. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 527. (Reel 9)
    - Burress, Jimmy, Frame(s) 253, Green Pastures. (Reel 5)
    - Burton, Jeff
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 224. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 290, Gunpoint. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 229, The Legend of Jimmy Blue Eyes. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 476, Planet of the Apes. (Reel 10)
    - Burwell, Evelyn
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 225. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 317-321, Hallelujah. (Reel 5)
    - Burwell, Myra, Frame(s) 117, Colored Players Film Company. (Reel 3)
    - Bush, Anita
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 226. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 268. (Reel 7)
    - Buster Keaton Story (Paramount, 1956); Frame(s) 227, Bill Walker. (Reel 2)
    - The Busy Body (Paramount, 1967); Frame(s) 228, Godfrey Cambridge. (Reel 2)
    - But Not For Me, (1959); Frame(s) 229, Ella Fitzgerald. (Reel 2)
    - Butler, Sarah, Frame(s) 545. (Reel 9)
    - Butler, Ted, Frame(s) 160-164, The Cool World. (Reel 3)
    - Butter, Charles, Frame(s) 3, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
    - Butterbeans and Suzie
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 230, Death. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 718, Nine Lives. (Reel 9)
    - By Right of Birth (Lincoln, 1920)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 2, Robert Abrams. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 50-56, Clarence Brooks. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 53, Deanwood Pictures Corporation. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 327-715, LMPPC. (Reel 7)
    - Byars, Rufus G., Frame(s) 232. (Reel 2)
    - Bye, Bye Braverman (7 Arts, 1967); Frame(s) 333. (Reel 2)
    - Byles, Louis, Frame(s) 231, The Crowning Experience. (Reel 2)
    - Byrd, Anthony
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 234. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 690, Voice of Conscience. (Reel 12)
    - Byrd, Carl, Frame(s) 235 *. (Reel 2)
    - Byron & Byron, Frame(s) 1, Four for Texas. (Reel 5)
  - C
    - Cabin in the Cotton, Frame(s) 237, Clarence Muse. (Reel 2)
    - Cabin in the Sky (MGM)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 262, Bill Bailey; 369, Vince Minelli. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 236. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 257, Leon James. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 296, Claude Marchant. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 906, Nicodemes Stewart. (Reel 11)
    - Cade, Rachael
      See Rachael Cade
    - Caesar and Cleopatra
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 18, Robert Adams. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 238, Eartha Kitt. (Reel 2)
    - Cahee, Regina
      See Cohee, Regina
    - Caine Mutiny (Columbia), Frame(s) 239, James Edwards. (Reel 2)
    - Cain's Hundred, (1961); Frame(s) 240, Dorothy Dandridge. (Reel 2)
    - Cairo (MGM, 1933); Frame(s) 241, Ethel Waters. (Reel 2)
    - Caleb Match, (1968); Frame(s) 242, Bernie Hamilton. (Reel 2)
    - Calhoun, Authur, Frame(s) 910, William Grant Still. (Reel 11)
    - California Straight Ahead (Universal, 19??); Frame(s) 244. (Reel 2)
    - Call Me Back
      Frame(s) see The Slender Thread
    - The Call of His People, (1921); Frame(s) 83-90, Reol Productions. (Reel 11)
    - Calling All Husbands (Warners, 1940); Frame(s) 246, Ernest True, Sam McDaniels. (Reel 2)
    - Calloway, Blanche, Frame(s) 523-524, Cozy Cole. (Reel 2)
    - Calloway, Cab
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 241, Ebony Parade; 556, The Berry Brothers; 264, 274, Pearl Bailey. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 247-256 *; 431 recording; 523-524, Cozy Cole. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 373, Billy Daniels. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 478, 629-672. (Reel 4)
    - Calloway, Chris
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 295, 301, Hello Dolly. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 252, Cab Calloway, Hugh Masakela. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 461, Career. (Reel 4)
    - Calloway, Ernest, Frame(s) 241, Reward. (Reel 1)
    - Calomee, Gloria
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 257, 505. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 235, The Reivers. (Reel 3)
    - Cavalcade of Negro Music, Frame(s) 17, Joe Adams. (Reel 1)
    - Calypso Heat Wave (Columbia, 1957); Frame(s) 259, Trenier Twins. (Reel 2)
    - Calypso Island, (1957); Frame(s) 260. (Reel 2)
    - Calypso Joe (Warner, 1957); Frame(s) 258, Herb Jeffries. (Reel 2)
    - Cambridge, Godfrey
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 261-284 *. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 10, Redd Foxx. (Reel 5)
    - Camby, William, Frame(s) 253, Green Pastures. (Reel 5)
    - Cameo Kirby (Fox, 1927); Frame(s) 285, George Reed & Noble Johnson. (Reel 2)
    - Cameron, Earl
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 286. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 291, Guns at Batasi. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 660, Simba. (Reel 11)
    - Cameron, Randy, Frame(s) 287. (Reel 2)
    - Campbell, C.B. Company, Frame(s) 288, The Negro of Today. (Reel 2)
    - Campbell, Choker, Frame(s) 591, Shake, Rattle & Roll. (Reel 11)
    - Campbell, Huntely, Frame(s) 289, Simba. (Reel 2)
    - Campbell, Milton, Frame(s) 1, 290, Bob Mathias Story. (Reel 2)
    - Campos, Rafael, Frame(s) 291, Dinah Washington. (Reel 2)
    - Can This Be Dixie? (Fox, 19??); Frame(s) 295, Hattie McDaniels. (Reel 2)
    - Canary Murder Case, Frame(s) 292, Oscar Smith. (Reel 2)
    - Candy (United Artists, 1968); Frame(s) 293, Sugar Ray Robinson. (Reel 2)
    - The Candy Web (Columbia, 1963); Frame(s) 294, Judy Pace. (Reel 2)
    - Canty, Marietta
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 296, A Man Called Peter. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 261, A Man Called Peter. (Reel 8)
    - Cape Smoke
      See Black Magic (Fox 1929)
    - Capers, Virginia
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 297, The Necessity Woman. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 301, The Necessity Woman. (Reel 9)
    - Caprice, (1967); Frame(s) 301B, Consuela Neal. (Reel 2)
    - Captain Buffalo (Warner Brothers, 1959); Frame(s) 299, Juano Hernandez & Woody Strode. (Reel 2)
    - Captain Flamingo, (1956); Frame(s) 300, Herb Jeffries. (Reel 2)
    - Captain Sinbad German (MGM, 1962); Frame(s) 301, Bernie Hamilton. (Reel 2)
    - The Caravan (Universal, 19??); Frame(s) 302-A, Noble Johnson. (Reel 2)
    - The Cardinal (Fox, 1939, 1969); Frame(s) 302-B-305, Ossie Davis, Eric Portman. (Reel 2)
    - Carey, Tim
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 438, Bed of Fear. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 306, Bed of Fear. (Reel 2)
    - Carib Gold, (1956); Frame(s) 309, Geoffrey Holder. (Reel 2)
    - Caribbean (Paramount, 1952); Frame(s) 307, Clarence Muse, Woody Strode. (Reel 2)
    - Caribbean Story, Frame(s) 308, Calla Scrivner. (Reel 2)
    - Carlisle, Una Mae, Frame(s) 310. (Reel 2)
    - Carlyle, Richard, Frame(s) 469-471, Hearts in Dixie. (Reel 5)
    - Carmen (Beta, 19??); Frame(s) 515, Grace Bumbry. (Reel 4)
    - Carmen Jones (Fox/play, 1955)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 17, Joe Adams. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 311-312. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 5-6, Muriel Rahn. (Reel 11)
    - Carney, Harry, Frame(s) 247, jam session. (Reel 2)
    - Carnival Fantastique, Frame(s) 314, Edric Conner. (Reel 2)
    - Carnival of Rhythm, Frame(s) 313, Katherine Dunham. (Reel 2)
    - Carol, Connie, Frame(s) 337, Rockin' the Blues. (Reel 11)
    - Carolina (Fox, 1934); Frame(s) 315, Stepin Fetchit. (Reel 2)
    - Carolina Blues (Columbia, 1944); Frame(s) 316, Harold Nicholas, 4 Step Brothers. (Reel 2)
    - Carolina Moon (Republic, 1940); Frame(s) 317, Etta McDaniels. (Reel 2)
    - Carpenter, Thelma
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 421, Count Basie. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 16, in Brazil. (Reel 6)
    - The Carpet baggers (Paramount, 1963); Frame(s) 318-319, Archie Moore. (Reel 2)
    - Carr, Georgia
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 166, Death. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 320. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 343, Handle with Care. (Reel 5)
    - Carr, Jack, Frame(s) 321, Wamba. (Reel 2)
    - Carr, Lawrence, Frame(s) 322. (Reel 2)
    - Carroll, Diahann
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 8, Academy Awards; 267, Pearl Bailey; Shirley Bassey; 465, 474, Harry Belafonte. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 82, 128, 146-147, Jim Brown; 273, Godfrey Cambridge; 323-353 * 353. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 532-637, Sidney Poitier. (Reel 10)
    - Carroll, Nansi, Frame(s) 507, Negro Entertainers. (Reel 4)
    - Carroll, Ted, Frame(s) 354-356. (Reel 2)
    - Carroll, Vinette, Frame(s) 357. (Reel 2)
    - Carruthers, Ben, Frame(s) 358, Shadows. (Reel 2)
    - Carry Me Back to Morningside Heights, (1965); Frame(s) 359, Sidney Poitier. (Reel 2)
    - Carson, Charles, Frame(s) 32, African Fury. (Reel 1)
    - Carson, Tee, Frame(s) 596, Ella Fitzgerald. (Reel 4)
    - Cartens, Marianne, Frame(s) 360, Rachael Cade. (Reel 2)
    - Carter, Ben
      See Carter, Benny
    - Carter, Benny
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 421, Count Basie. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 361-362; 524, Cozy Cole. (Reel 2)
    - Carter, Carol
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 363, career. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 143, Giovanni Sposi. (Reel 5)
    - Carter, Dr. Fred, Frame(s) 364, 458, A Child Waits. (Reel 2)
    - Carter, Jack
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 216, Domino Production. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 511, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
    - Carter, Mel
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 365, Enter Laughing. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 498, Enter Laughing. (Reel 4)
    - Carter, Phil, Frame(s) 366. (Reel 2)
    - Carter, Terry, Frame(s) 367, Parrish. (Reel 2)
    - Carthage in Flames (Italian, 1968); Frame(s) 368, Edith Peters. (Reel 2)
    - Cartlett, Sid
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 26, Boy, What a Girl! (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 511, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
    - Carver, George Washington, (1954)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 38, Bill Alexander. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 280, experimental film. (Reel 2)
    - Casablance (Warner Brothers, 1942); Frame(s) 369, Clarence Muse & Dooley Wilson. (Reel 2)
    - Casanova Man (Italian, 1955); Frame(s) 370, Billy Daniels. (Reel 2)
    - Casbah (Universal, 1947); Frame(s) 371, Katherine Dunham. (Reel 2)
    - Casey, Bernie
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 381-384. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 293, Guns of the Magnificent 7. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 131, The Informer. (Reel 6)
    - Cash, Rosalind, Frame(s) 544. (Reel 9)
    - Cass Timberlane (MGM, 1947)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 372, Jessica Grayson. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 231, Jessica Grayson. (Reel 5)
    - The Cast (Magazine), Frame(s) 625-643, Negroes in theatre. (Reel 9)
    - Casting
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 2,4, Black Actors Directory of 1923; 9, 10, 304-306, Negro actors. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 263, Thunderbolt. (Reel 12)
    - Castle Keep (Filmways, 1968); Frame(s) 373. (Reel 2)
    - Cat Ballou (Warner Brothers, 1964); Frame(s) 374, Nat King Cole. (Reel 2)
    - A Cat Called Jesus, Frame(s) 375-377, controversy. (Reel 2)
    - Catch My Soul, Frame(s) 378. (Reel 2)
    - Cato, Minto, Frame(s) 378, Benny Goodman Story. (Reel 2)
    - Cavalry (Republic, 1936); Frame(s) 385, Martin Turner. (Reel 2)
    - Cavanaugh, Page Trio, Frame(s) 386, Romance on the High Seas. (Reel 2)
    - Cease Fire, Frame(s) 435, Johnnie Mayes. (Reel 2)
    - Cele, Willard, Frame(s) 387. (Reel 2)
    - The Centurions (Red Lion, 1965); Frame(s) 388, Gordon Heath. (Reel 2)
    - A Certain Smile (RKO, 1958); Frame(s) 389, Johnny Mathias. (Reel 2)
    - Chaino, Frame(s) 390. (Reel 2)
    - Champs-Elysee, Frame(s) 391, Sugar Ray Robinson. (Reel 2)
    - Change of Mind, (1968); Frame(s) 392. (Reel 2)
    - Chapman, Edward
      See Ballantyne, Lon
    - The Chariotters
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 393. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 156. (Reel 11)
    - Charity, (1968); Frame(s) 394, Sammy Davis, Jr. (Reel 2)
    - Charles, Ezzard
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 398. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 357, Mau Mau Drums. (Reel 8)
    - Charles, Ray, Frame(s) 399-429; 600, Nat King Cole. (Reel 2)
    - Charlie Chan, Frame(s) 395-397, Mantan Moreland. (Reel 2)
    - Charlie Chan in Egypt (Fox, 1935); Frame(s) 396, Steppin Fetchit. (Reel 2)
    - The Charmer (Paramount, 1925); Frame(s) 430. (Reel 2)
    - The Charming Enemy (Ital.), Frame(s) 431, Ben Turpin. (Reel 2)
    - Charter Pilot (Fox, 1940); Frame(s) 432, Etta McDaniel. (Reel 2)
    - The Chase (Columbia, 1955); Frame(s) 433-434. (Reel 2)
    - Chasing Trouble (Monogram, 1940); Frame(s) 436, Mantan Moreland. (Reel 2)
    - Chatman, Frank, Frame(s) 626, Foolish Lives. (Reel 4)
    - Chatterbox (Republic, 1943); Frame(s) 437, Mills Brothers. (Reel 2)
    - Chavence, Janice, Frame(s) 56, Dear Negro. (Reel 4)
    - Che (Fox, 1968); Frame(s) 438, Max Julien, Woody Strode. (Reel 2)
    - Cheaters, Frame(s) 439, Louise Beavers. (Reel 2)
    - Checker, Chubby
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 440-448. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 220, Don't Knock the Twist. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 190, It's Trad, Dad. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 405, Twist Around the Clock. (Reel 12)
    - The Chelsea Flat (London, 1967); Frame(s) 449, Joanna Moore. (Reel 2)
    - Chenault, Lawrence
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 450. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 117, Colored Players Film Corporation. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 392-562, Oscar Micheaux. (Reel 8)
    - Chester, Alfred, Frame(s) 511, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
    - Chester, C.L., Frame(s) 9. (Reel 9)
    - Chester, George, Frame(s) 451. (Reel 2)
    - Chester, Slick, Frame(s) 394, Harlem is Harlem. (Reel 5)
    - Chestnutt, Charles, Frame(s) 27, House Behind the Cedars. (Reel 6)
    - Chiari, Walter, Frame(s) 452, The Little Hut. (Reel 2)
    - Chicago Calling (United Artists, 1961); Frame(s) 453, Roy Glenn. (Reel 2)
    - Les Chiffoniers D'emmaus (French, 19??); Frame(s) 454, Babe Wallace. (Reel 2)
    - A Child is Waiting, Frame(s) 455, Juanita More. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 33, Jamie Rawls. (Reel 11)
    - A Child Waits, (1963); Frame(s) 458, Fred Carter. (Reel 2)
    - Childress, Alice, Frame(s) 292, Claire Leyba. (Reel 7)
    - Childress, Alvin
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 72-73, Amos; 121-125, Anna Lucasta. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 456-457. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 270, Man in the Net. (Reel 8)
    - The China Gate (Fox, 1957); Frame(s) 459-461, Nat King Cole. (Reel 2)
    - The Chinese Ring (Monogram, 1947); Frame(s) 462, Mantan Moreland. (Reel 2)
    - Choice, (1964); Frame(s) 463, Goldwater campaign. (Reel 2)
    - Chrisman, Gertrude, Frame(s) 693-709, Realization of Negro's Ambition. (Reel 7)
    - Christ-Mark Productions, Frame(s) 468, Sammy Davis, Jr. (Reel 2)
    - Christie Comedies, Frame(s) 464-467. (Reel 2)
    - Christmas, Leonard, Frame(s) 400, Harlem Rides the Range. (Reel 5)
    - Chubasco (Warner Brothers, 1968); Frame(s) 469, Ron Rich. (Reel 2)
    - Cimarron (RKO, 1931); Frame(s) 470, Eugene Jackson. (Reel 2)
    - The Cimarron Kid (Universal, 1951); Frame(s) 471, Frank Silvera. (Reel 2)
    - Cincinnati Kid (MGM, 1965); Frame(s) 472, Cab Calloway. (Reel 2)
    - Cincone, Don
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 234, The Art of Love. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 476, The Art of Love. (Reel 2)
    - Cinderella Swings (RKO, 1943); Frame(s) 473, Willie Best. (Reel 2)
    - Cinderfella, (1959); Frame(s) 474, Count Basie. (Reel 2)
    - Cinema Corps of the Eastern Region of Nigeria, Frame(s) 475, Eartha Kitt. (Reel 2)
    - City Beneath the Sea (Universal, 1953); Frame(s) 477, Wally Strode. (Reel 2)
    - Clancy Street Boys (Monogram, 1943); Frame(s) 478, Sammy Morrison. (Reel 2)
    - Clanton, Hampton
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 479, The Cool World. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 160-164, The Cool World. (Reel 3)
    - Clarence, the Cross-eyed Lion, (1964); Frame(s) 480, Naamon Brown. (Reel 2)
    - Clarke, Alberta, Frame(s) 481, receives award. (Reel 2)
    - Clarke, Byron
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 482, The Lawman. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 194, The Lawman. (Reel 7)
    - Clarke, Shirley
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 479, The Cool World. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 144, The Connection; 160-164, The Cool World. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 673, Portrait of Jason. (Reel 10)
    - Claude, Suzan, Frame(s) 493. (Reel 2)
    - Clavell, James, Frame(s) 163, Glory Tent. (Reel 5)
    - Claw, (1927); Frame(s) 483, Ernest Wilson. (Reel 2)
    - Clay, Cassius
      See Ali, Mohammed
    - Clay, Mark
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 437. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 494. (Reel 2)
    - Clay, Willie
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 398, 492, Mau Mau Drums. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 357. (Reel 8)
    - Clayton, Ed, Frame(s) 495, death. (Reel 2)
    - Clayton, William, Jr., Frame(s) 117, Colored Players Film Corporation, 1926. (Reel 3)
    - Cleaver, Eldridge, Frame(s) 524-571, Negroes in Moving Pictures. (Reel 9)
    - Cleaver, Kathleen, Frame(s) 404, movie role. (Reel 9)
    - Cleaver, Zeldo, Frame(s) 402-407. (Reel 1)
    - Clements, Lynda (Rosalyn Anita), Frame(s) 496. (Reel 2)
    - Cleopatra (Fox, 1960); Frame(s) 497. (Reel 2)
    - Cleveland, James, Frame(s) 512, Negro entertainers. (Reel 4)
    - Clifford, J.W.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 497. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 198-202, Cosmopolitan Pictures Corporation. (Reel 3)
    - Clinical Film Corporation, Frame(s) 500, medical films for Black doctors. (Reel 2)
    - Clisby, Jack
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 236, Argus Pictures. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 501, death. (Reel 2)
    - The Clock Strikes Three, Frame(s) 502, Diahann Carroll. (Reel 2)
    - Close Harmony (Paramount, 1929); Frame(s) 503, Oscar Smith. (Reel 2)
    - Clough, Inez
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 381-382, Easy Money. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 266, Ties of Blood. (Reel 12)
    - The Clovers, Frame(s) 335, Rock 'n Roll Jamboree. (Reel 11)
    - Cobb, Arnett, Frame(s) 339, Lionel Hampton. (Reel 5)
    - Cochran, Wayne, Frame(s) 36. (Reel 2)
    - Cochrane, Myron, Frame(s) 243, Winston Affair. (Reel 2)
    - Cohee, Regina
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 33, Afro-American Film Exhibitors. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 405-409, A. Robert Porter. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 118, Lure of a Woman. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 718, Progress Pictures Association. (Reel 10)
    - Cole, Carol
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 504-522; 527-619. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 413, Negro entertainers. (Reel 4)
    - Cole, Celeste, Frame(s) 536-538, The Exile. (Reel 4)
    - Cole, Cozy
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 174, movie musicals; 284, Pearl Bailey. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 523-524, Carmen Jones. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 159, Glenn Miller Story. (Reel 5)
    - Cole, Ike, Frame(s) 525; 527-619, Nat King Cole. (Reel 2)
    - Cole, Maria, Frame(s) 505-522; 526-619, Nat King Cole. (Reel 2)
    - Cole, Mildred
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 402, Billy Eckstine. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 51, Hurry, Charlie, Hurry. (Reel 6)
    - Cole, Nat King
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 51, Shep Allen; 85-87, Why Stars Go Broke; 268, Pearl Bailey. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 277, school honor; 402-429, Ray Charles; 505-522, Carol Cole; 526-527, Marie Cole; 527-619 *. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 1-96; 468, Sammy Davis, Jr. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 100, Marvin Gaye; 346-357, W.C. Handy. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 45, Studio Film Company 1095, Roosevelt Zanders. (Reel 12)
    - Cole, Natalie, Frame(s) 504-522; 526-619, Nat King Cole. (Reel 2)
    - Cole, Robert
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 153, J. Rosamond Johnson. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 450, J. Rosamond Johnson. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 910, William Grant Still. (Reel 11)
    - Coleman, Ornette, Frame(s) 414, Miles Davis. (Reel 3)
    - Coleman, Paralee, Frame(s) 97, The Bargain Hunt. (Reel 3)
    - Coleman, Warren, Frame(s) 107. (Reel 3)
    - Coles & Atkins, Frame(s) 283, Pearl Bailey. (Reel 1)
    - Colette, Gabriele, Frame(s) 98. (Reel 3)
    - College Scandal (Paramount, 1935); Frame(s) 100, Oscar Smith. (Reel 3)
    - Collette, Buddy, Frame(s) 337 Trauma. (Reel 12)
    - Collette, Florine, Frame(s) 101, Mauri Lynn. (Reel 3)
    - Colley, Don Pedro, Frame(s) 102. (Reel 3)
    - Collins, Barry, Frame(s) 103, Time of the Heathen. (Reel 3)
    - Collins, Bobbie J., Frame(s) 104. (Reel 3)
    - Collins, Claude
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 466, Christie Comedies. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 149, The Lady Fare. (Reel 7)
    - Collins, Janet
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 105. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 92, Carmen DeLavallade 299-300, Katherine Dunham. (Reel 4)
    - Collins, Leroy
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 241, Astor Pictures. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 106, The Betrayal. (Reel 3)
    - Collins, Valerie, Frame(s) 187-199, Gone With The Wind. (Reel 5)
    - The Color of Love (English, 1966); Frame(s) 109, Gordon Heath. (Reel 3)
    - Colorado Sundown (Republic, 1952); Frame(s) 108, Louise Beavers. (Reel 3)
    - Colored Americans War Film, (1918)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 110-111. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 9, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
    - Colored American Winning His Suit (Doug., 1919)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 112. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 10, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
    - Colored and Indian Film Company, (1917)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 113, List of Films. (Reel 3)